Good morning, everybody.
Just as a reminder, I'm letting
everybody in from the lobby at this
time. So, welcome to the meeting,
everyone. I'm Dominic Zerlo. It'll be a
moment or two before everybody is in
from the waiting room. So, in the
meantime, just to remind everybody who
is joining us today, this is the dosage
administration and clinical practice
committee with Ian Dunn as the chair.
Please remember this meeting is being
recorded, so please keep your language
appropriate. And
uh at this point, I will turn it on over
to you, Ian.
So, thank you, everybody.
>> Thank you, everyone, for being here. My
name is Ian Dunn. I'm the chair of the
dosage administration and clinical
practice committee. And we are here
today to look over preparation sessions.
I believe we've we've done a lot of
discussion over the the past three or
four meetings on preparation sessions.
So, I think this is finally
where we're at. We're just going to read
through it again. Once again, open
discussion, see what needs to be
changed, what we may have overlooked in
the last meetings,
and go from there. At this time, I will
allow anyone that would like to
participate to introduce themselves.
>> All right. And just as a reminder, you
can raise your hand by clicking the icon
at the top of the hand that says raise.
And then we can enable your mic from
there. And you're also welcome to
introduce yourself in the chat if you
would prefer to do that as well.
>> Okay, I see no hands, but I did see in
the chat Kate Hawk, a Santa Fe trauma
therapist and trainer.
>> And then again in chat, James Brown,
PharmD.
Then I see Sky Rivers, um, SFR sitting
in.
Kiyana McKenzie, a naturopathic doctor
and retired midwife. Thank you all for
being here. Don Moser from Las Vegas,
New Mexico. Thank you for being here.
Catherine Warnock, a licensed counselor
in Las Cruces. Thank you for being here.
All right, and then I'm seeing no more
introductions. So, uh, Jorge, if I could
have you present the preparation session
document.
Perfect. All right, and then I will go
ahead and post it in the chat as well.
So, to anyone who has been attending our
meetings before, which I believe is the
majority of you, you should be pretty,
um, familiar with this document. It's
what we've been going over over
psychological preparation versus
administrative preparation.
So, the psychological preparation, this
is where that psychodel- psychedelic
therapist that we had discussed, um,
would be involved in the psychological
preparation process and establish that
clinical foundation for treatment. So,
timing, this phase would occur first. It
allows the therapist to determine
medical appropriateness and approve or
defer participation based on safety.
I That means if they are not
appropriate, they should be referred out
to someone that can help treat their
ailment to make them appropriate, not
necessarily just given a rejection
letter and sent on their way.
For medical history, the therapist
should conduct a biopsychosocial
assessment and review medical medical
including medication interactions and
contraindications. Again, these are not
necessarily new information that we have
to treat them. The board will provide um
risk stratification methods to um
address medication interactions and
contraindications specifically. That way
it's just more of a compare list against
list and we don't have to make them into
you know, an entire 4 years of medical
school in order to become a psychedelic
therapist, especially when they already
have
um a clinical counselor or social work
license or something like that.
In terms of intention setting and
objectives,
the therapist facilitates the discussion
of patient goals, their intentions, and
expectations for the session to
establish a psychological framework. We
orient them to set the patient's
physical, emotional, and psychological
readiness
and help them navigate those set factors
and potential psychological challenges.
During this preparation, we would also
do clinical safety planning. The
therapist evaluates the risks for
adverse responses, creates the formal
safety plan, and the therapist should
also perform an assessment of the
patient support system. Now, this is
going to vary between different approved
locations. If you have an approved
location that's 5 minutes from a
hospital, their emergency plan may be,
well, ambulance them there. If you are
in rural New Mexico, you may have a
different set of policies, and we're
just saying that the therapist should be
um taking those factors into
consideration and creating a formal
safety plan before the patient is
actually administered psilocybin.
Uh we talked about a matrix. So, that
assessment of suitable release
environment, support system, and
aftercare. So, what they are going to
experience once they leave um that
approved facility. And are they going to
be able to manage on their own um once
they are outside of uh the medical
psilocybin system's care. And so, we're
just wanting to make sure we're not
sending anyone into a dangerous or
potentially harmful situation.
Next is therapist should provide general
education on the who, what, where or
who, what, why, and how of psilocybin
and potential adverse effects in an
easy-to-read digestible format for
patients.
Um
dosing and tearing. This is where the
therapist would say, "Okay, you know,
you're on
um
an SSRI. Those have been shown to have
blunting effects."
Um so, we're going to go ahead and give
you a higher dose so that you can
actually um achieve therapeutic
potential.
And you know, determining that to the
patient. Uh in terms of referral,
this is what we kind of talked about
earlier, but if a patient is determined
to be clinically inappropriate, the
therapist is responsible for referring
them to a primary care provider or other
appropriate treatment avenue. What we're
trying to avoid with this is that just
getting slammed with a rejection letter
and not knowing where to go forward.
Um cultural and spiritual alignment,
you'll actually find this in both
administrative and psychological
preparation. And it's just using that
trauma-informed and culturally competent
communication.
This is probably the least enforceable
of the of the mechanisms here because
it's really hard to tell someone um
it's really hard to post facto tell if
someone used trauma-informed and
culturally competent communication, but
that should still be the gold standard
within our program.
Uh determination of readiness. And then
this is the part where the patient is
physically, emotionally, mentally ready
for psilocybin treatment. This would be
right before, you know, they go in and
just saying, "Hey, um
checking in, making sure that everything
is still in the state that it was
um, during initial assessment.
Um,
then we go to administrative
preparation. So, this is the
facilitator. This is a non-clinical
role.
Um, the facilitator conducts
administrative preparation in
coordination with the psychedelic
therapist. So, we've already defined
these roles. What we're doing here is
working to define um,
what the difference between those roles
are because preparation can often be
mixed into administrative and
psychologic.
But, by separating them out, we allow
the licensed um, healthcare provider to
provide the
um, psychological experience, whereas a
lot of the administrative tasks we can
defer to our facilitators.
So, their timing. The final preparation
session must be conducted by the
facilitator who will be present during
the administration session. I don't
think anyone wants um,
to undergo a psilocybin experience with
um,
no familiar faces in the room.
And so, I think it's important that they
at least know who is going to be with
them, um, their energy, make sure that
everything flows.
Um, informed consent. The facilitator is
responsible for obtaining and
documenting informed consent during the
session. Correct fit. The session is the
primary opportunity for the patient and
facilitator to ensure the rapport is a
good fit for the patient's goals.
And this just means, you know,
each person is going to have a different
alignment. Um,
you've probably experienced it, you
know, going out in the world and you
have some co-workers you really like and
you have some co-workers that they're
okay, you just don't vibe with them the
same way. And so, what this correct fit
is meant to do is to say, if you have
ever met someone that you don't vibe
with, we don't want to force them into a
box and say, "This is going to be your
facilitator." because at the end of the
day, um,
you are going to be going undergoing
immense emotional um,
processes and spiritual processes. And
so, ensuring that the person you're with
is a good fit for you is incredibly
important.
Logistics and boundaries. Um, this would
include establishing boundaries such as
touch, um, written disclosures, and
orienting the patient to the
non-clinical scope of the facilitator.
Um, orientation to setting. So, we had
set with the, um,
psychedelic therapist, we have setting
with the facilitator. So, the
facilitator orients the patient to the
physical environment where the session
will occur. This includes reviewing
environmental conditions, lighting,
temperature, sound, explaining privacy
measures, and ensuring the patient is
comfortable with the facility layout and
their accommodations.
Escalation. The facilitator is
responsible for knowing how to escalate
medical or psychological concerns to the
psychedelic therapist or emergency
services. This should be part of the
orientation.
Cultural and spiritual alignment. Using
trauma-informed and culturally competent
communication, the therapist ensures
alignment regarding any ceremonial,
cultural, or spiritual elements that may
be present. And then materials. This is
the, um, more so in the administration
than in the
preparation part, but it's just letting
you know that the facilitator would be
the one providing the materials for the
patient self-administration in
accordance in accordance with the
therapist direction.
And then we have some combined timing
and compliance standards. So, the total
duration, patients shall complete at
least two preparation sessions totaling
no less than three hours prior to
administration, at least one to be
dedicated to psycholo- psychological
preparation, and at least another to
administrative preparation. And then an
in-person requirement, where feasible,
at least one hour of total preparation
time shall be conducted in person. And
then while we recognize that this is not
always possible, um, due to rural and
equity and access concerns, um, that's
why we included that where feasible. If
it is a
huge mountain to jump over to have an
in-person, then an adjustment should be
allowed.
And then sequence psychological
preparation must be completed and
clinical appropriateness determined
before the final administrative
preparation session is concluded.
Just saying that before we get all of
our informed consent that
orientation is setting all of those
other aspects that we want them to have
already been medically cleared. We just
don't want them to get to the final step
and then
get hit with a stop.
And then documentation all of
the things that are being done are
documented. So that was a lot of
information. So I am going to open for
any discussion on any of the parts.
>> All right, and I see Katherine Warnock's
hand up first.
And Katherine, I've allowed your mic and
you can unmute.
>> Good morning.
Thank you again for all this. This is
pretty awesome.
I wanted to ask a little bit more about
the timing
with respect to that final session.
It says no less than 24 hours and no
more than 30 days.
I often do the last
I call it a group meeting where the
night before or the evening or afternoon
before I have everybody see the set
setting. It's like a a meeting where all
participants are present. I'm curious
why no less than 24 hours.
And then I'm also wondering about the no
more than 30 days. I think that we need
to qualify something in there around as
long as nothing's changed meaning they
need to have like there wherever they're
going to dose needs to stay the same. So
if it's been 20 days, that's okay as
long as nothing's changed about their
environment. I I it's important that it
that you know the whole point of them
kind of seeing the environment is
establishing set and setting, and it's
important that nothing be altered or
changed. So, I don't know, 30 days seems
like a long time for me, but I can
understand there might be certain
circumstances where that's the case. I
just think we need to specify
that it needs to be the same as, you
know, what they are shown needs to be
the same as what they're going to
experience.
>> You are absolutely right. Let me see.
So, I'm going to add to orientation to
setting, um
what the patient
sees in preparation
should
shall be the same, shall
not go any under any changes
before
administration.
>> Yeah.
>> Cool.
All right. So, um now the orientation to
setting is um the facilitator orients
the patient to the physical environment
where the session will occur, includes
reviewing environmental conditions,
explaining privacy measures, um the
facility layout and accommodations, and
what the patient sees in preparation
shall not go under any changes before
administration.
He's in
All right?
>> And then the less than 24 hours, I'm
curious about that. Tell me more about
what the intent is around that.
>> The intent was just to make sure that
like
um that last preparation and the like
what I was envisioning was someone going
in for setting like 5 minutes before
their [laughter]
session. So, I would be okay with saying
maybe 6 hours? Like if cuz that
presenting it at the night and then
doing it in the morning, that would make
sense to me. There's still a pause in in
consciousness and like time to reflect.
But um
>> I agree. It shouldn't be 5 minutes,
right? Like
it needs to be like they need to have
time to digest it, make sure they're
comfortable with it before the next
session. So, I I I get that. I think I
just think 24 hours like So, what I
usually do try to do is make sure it's
still daylight when they see it so that
it will look like daylight the next day.
Like I'm trying to make sure the
conditions are similar, but it is yeah,
the next
it is the night before the afternoon
before. So.
>> So, would you be okay with 12 or 6
hours?
>> 12 or 6, yeah. Or even just overnight
would be good. Like
Like needs to at least be the previous
day. I mean, I guess you could have
somebody come check it out and then come
back 6 hours later.
Um
But yeah, I think 12 12 is good.
>> Perfect.
>> Thank you.
>> Mhm. Of course. Thank you.
>> All right. And next we've got Leda
Fattemi and Leda, your mic is enabled.
You can unmute.
>> Hi, good morning everybody.
Thank you for this. This is great. My
question is um
as we're setting these rules out, is it
that
you know, the word psychedelic therapist
was used several times. Now, and then
the separation between the psychedelic
therapist doing the preparation and
integration perhaps and someone else,
the facilitator
doing the session is being talked about.
Now, oftentimes what's happening on the
ground is that one person is doing the
entire thing.
Um
is that are we being flexible here or
what and then you know, we have
psychedelic coaches doing this work. We
have physicians doing this work. We have
nurses doing this work. We have NPs,
PAs. So, they're not therapists.
Um
I'm sorry. I'm driving to patients and
you may hear little uh little chiming in
the background as I'm navigating. But,
he that was my question. The kind of
those roles, do they have to be separate
and different people holding those
uh spaces in the container? Can it be
the same person as we see it happen
you know, what's happening in the
community or they have to be you know,
that's I have a question about that and
also that role of the therapist. Does it
have because when we say therapist, that
is a particular certification
and licensing that's different than a
social worker, than a counselor, than a
physician that on and on.
Um
yeah.
>> So, in regards to So, one person could
hold multiple licenses. So, they could
be both the facilitator and the um
the
psychedelic therapist. Um
So, that wouldn't really be an issue in
terms of
um
what would
like the psychedelic what ever we call
it in the recommendations is not what
they have to call themselves.
Um so, we've gone so around between
practitioners, psychedelic therapists um
psychedelic trained therapist um and
different formulations, but and
it's just the position that they hold.
And if we look at the actual what we had
said was a psychedelic therapist
was any
um
person licensed by the
Department of Health per the rules. So,
when we go through that, it doesn't
necessarily have to be that person. We
just wanted that um
So, what the difference Sorry, I mixed
that up. What the difference between the
facilitator and the psychedelic
therapist is is that licensure. So, if
someone has licensure, they can be both
the psychedelic therapist and the
facilitator, but if they do not have the
licensure, then they would could only be
the facilitator is kind of the rule
around that.
>> Got you. Got you. Thank you so much. And
yeah, just making sure that that's clear
in the in the document. Like, you know,
this is what we mean. Kind of like a
legend.
So, people can refer to that language
cuz I think that's really important for
us to be clear on. But, thank you for
that clarification. That makes complete
sense.
Yeah, thank you.
>> Thank you.
>> All right. Next, we've got Chris
Piskeski and Chris who are mics enabled
and you can unmute.
>> Good morning, everyone.
Um first, I'd like to
apologize
that I got up in this meeting last time
and I'm sorry to all of you. Um
>> [clears throat]
>> I'll find a better way to express my
frustrations in the future.
Um
I guess I've been spending a lot of time
thinking about this
this
I have to wonder if we're
kind of coming at this from the wrong
direction. This doesn't seem
you know, patient-focused
to me.
Like we're pigeonholing people into
certain roles, which
>> [sighs]
>> um doesn't
really allow
you know,
um
people to utilize their lived experience
or
or just their natural talents
in this area. There's some really good
practitioners that I know that are not
clinical and
there's good clinical practitioners,
too. Um
but
I don't
think we need to focus on who does what
as much as
what the people that are
participating in this program need.
And
you know, I grew up in an era and a
culture
that
there's a lot of stigma surrounding
mental health, you know? And I I think
back
to
my old self
and how I would navigate this program
and the
the common
phrase that
coming to mind that as I think how I
would have to go through this is that
you can't get there from here.
Um
And so
I just hope we set up the rules
in a way that allows
this to evolve.
Um and as, you know, our
small body of facilitators grows and
becomes more experienced that they
uh
can
maybe take lead on this a little bit
more because this is
this is very
mental health professional-centric and
there's nothing wrong with that, but it
just
it doesn't always work that way, you
know, I see a therapist now, but it took
me several years
to sure
comfortable with
>> [snorts]
>> with talking to a therapist and I'm
grateful for that relationship now, but
it it wouldn't have happened any other
way.
Um
and so
I don't know. I just
we uh we keep the participant more in
mind than pigeonholing
people and thank you all for your time.
I take it
but if you'll let ex-
earlier
in, I would vote no on this.
>> Thank you.
And James.
>> Morning everyone. Um
Ian, great start, but I think uh one
thing that we're missing that we see and
that I've used before is a bill of
rights.
I think we have the confidentiality
statement in there, that's great, but we
do use
a bill of rights for the patients, you
know, and
going back to Chris's point, that kind
of focuses more back on the patient
side. I think we need to kind of include
a few more things for patient stuff
here.
Um and that would be a bill of rights.
We need that for sure.
And they need to review that both
sessions.
Um what about other treatment
modalities? I I think there's kind of an
open open door there for that as far as
you know, what else can we use or what
else is going to be allowed to be used
um for those modalities? And again, I'm
very open with those modalities, but if
they're going to be doing breathing,
yoga, music, I really think that in a
that might be in the consent form, but
you know, that needs to be kind of
talked about and discussed because that
kind of goes back to that individual
safety plan again.
I don't see that in this form as much
um about uh safety focus. And so, I'm
kind of looking at harm reduction and
safety focus on that view.
And I think we need to beef that up a
little bit here, Ian and group. Um I
think there needs to be uh some type of
review of a transportation plan in this
um and that needs to be done in the
preparation session. And there also
needs to be done um
that biasness.
So, I just think we need a few more
forms and and like data points to cover.
Um this is very extensive paperwork and
we need to make sure we're covering all
bases here prior to
you know, the administration actually
occurring. And so, I think that starts
in the preparation again.
Um and so, we just need to kind of
include some of those things like the
Bill of Rights, what other modalities
are we going to use, a transportation
plan again, specifically what safety
plan are we using for each patient? You
know, again, that's individualized, but
we need to have that stuff done in
preparation and administration so that
everybody understands what's the
transportation, what's the safety
um and stuff like that. Um but I think
we have a good start, but my that focus
was more on confidentiality and privacy
of the actual patient uh versus the
facilitator. Thank you.
>> Perfect, and thank you. Um I actually
think we do need a patient Bill of
Rights of some sort. Um we can work on
that as a separate
I think it would make this document way
long if we included a Bill of Rights in
it. I did forget when I was um
transferring over the information from
the other one, the transportation plan.
So, thank you for bringing that up. I
will go ahead and add that. Um and then
other modalities, I believe, was the
other um thing you brought up. So, other
modalities are going to be used.
And the patient must be notified and
agree.
Um
And then
Jessica?
>> Hello. Hi, everyone. Um
I am just a little bit stuck still on
the correct fit and the timing of the
administration or the administrative
prep session.
Um and this is because I'm looking at it
as like that final preparation session
would be the potentially the first time
that the client is meeting the
facilitator. And if that's being done 6
to 12 hours before the session, and it's
not a good fit, um
then we're running into an issue as
well. Um and as a psychedelic therapist
/ facilitator myself, like the entire
the rapport that I'm building with the
client is done through that
psychological preparation and through
the preparation process. And so I'm I
myself I'm just stuck on the facilitator
meeting someone
12 to 24 hours before a session, and
then potentially that client then comes
back to me for integration. I wasn't
involved at all in that facilitation
session. All of it's kind of being
relayed um just on what the client can
remember or what the facilitator is
observing. Um
I just want to throw that out there
because that's just
what I'm kind of struggled with, I
guess, with this process.
I don't know if there's a a fix for it,
um but I just wanted to share this.
>> Yeah, so I think one of the things um
that may have been missing was
the psychedelic therapist is not like
off-site. In general, they're supposed
to be over the
facilitators. There are more
facilitators in the facility, but that
psychedelic therapist should still be
there.
Um for that purpose of escalation if
necessary,
um
and
>> [clears throat]
>> for general care of the client. The only
thing that the facilitator has is more
um they have less patients, so they
would be able to be more in their room
with them. But in terms of what we are
taking away from those sessions, the
psychedelic therapist would have been
there to, you know, make observations,
take notes. If the facilitator said,
"Hey, this seems important." They can go
and let them know. Um very similar to
how like um in a hospital, the a doctor
can have 100 patients, but they end up
with um
teams of nurses who actually are by the
bedside. That doesn't mean they don't do
their own assessment or collect data. It
just means that um
it allows them to get to more patients.
>> Okay. Thank you for clarifying cuz I
hadn't seen that anywhere that the
psychedelic therapist would also be on
site at the same time that the dosing is
occurring. Uh Um it seems to me like it
would all be completely separate.
>> Yeah, so this for this document they are
separated out cuz it's the separation of
their specific roles.
Um but in terms of
what they will do in practice, it will
be a psychedelic therapist and then a
facilitator. That's why a psychedelic
therapist can be a facilitator, but a
facilitator on his own cannot be a
psychedelic therapist. Um
it allows that there to be that person
there who is going to be there for
integration, who is going to
um you know, assess and who can provide
psychological assistance if necessary.
Um
I do appreciate the comment.
>> Yeah, I got you. Thank you. Thank you
for clarifying that.
>> All right, and uh next we've got Kate
Hawk and I have enabled your mic.
>> Good morning, everyone. Yeah, I really
appreciate how Ian you keep us forging
ahead and then there's room for
everybody to
participate and contribute here. I'm you
know, I'm wrapping my
>> [laughter]
>> my boggled mind around all of this. I I
mean I think it it makes a lot of sense.
I also agree with Jessica. Um you know,
there's ideal conditions and practices
and then we really are aiming for
affordability and accessibility
and with flexibility while still having
the quality.
Um so as a person who is not licensed by
choice but has lots of experience
um you know, I feel like this is we're
taking all these little steps as a in a
work in progress and just your mention
of well, there could be a facilitator
with a person who's at the moment at
least being called a psychedelic
therapist and then there could be a
number of facilitators since that
actually sitting with people during the
medicine session is time intensive
and may not be limited have to be
limited to licensed people. Uh I
appreciate how we're trying to work this
out and stay within the bounds of the
medical psilocybin act, which you know,
has certain qualifications.
So, um
I I had questions about clarification.
They're becoming more clear, and I just
want to, you know, acknowledge that
we're balancing these different factors
in the process, and I really appreciate
how the process is going. Thank you.
>> Well, thank you, K. I appreciate all of
you for being here today and
participating. Even
um the smallest detail if I added down,
it's something I didn't think of, and I
genuine genuinely appreciate it.
>> All right. And next, we've got Anika
Washington.
And I have enabled your mic.
>> Awesome. Good morning, everyone. Hello.
I am super excited about this and and
seeing the formation um of these
details. This really seems from the
perspective of individual care. I'm
curious if there'll be a subset of there
needs to be a subset in consideration of
group care.
That's my question today. Thank you.
>> Yeah, I think group care
has almost
a
specialized
type of care. Um in that I think we need
to lay it down a basis for the majority
of patients, at least in solo care, and
then we can make um the group care
requirements cuz I
it's hard for me to base, well, what is
a group need in addition to what a solo
writer needs?
Um
without knowing exactly what we are
going to have the solo writer need. So,
that's why we're here first, but I do
like your idea. It It's coming up. It's
in the works. Um
we just need to get some other things
first.
>> Okay, as long as it's in the works.
Thank you, Ian.
>> All right. And then, um does
Do you guys want some more time to just
take this preparation session and
document home, digest it, or are would
you guys be okay with a vote today?
>> Okay. Now, um let's see.
Yeah, see Eileen has commented in there
she can't unmute. Um
I think Yeah, I would like her comments
to be read. Let's see. So, wasn't So,
looks like the first one wasn't there
discussion around reducing preparation
time for people who need multiple dosing
sessions?
And then, uh to Jessica's point, I guess
it depends on the patient needs. I think
that therapists and facilitators can
decide what they want to offer and
require in addition to these
requirements.
Uh the patient can choose what they
want. Some patients might not care who
is facilitating.
>> And then, to go up with um what Eileen
said, sorry, sometimes Teams doesn't
notify the presenters when there's a
chat message. So, if we ever miss it,
it's It's our fault. Blame Microsoft.
Um, but
wasn't So, yes, there was. I went ahead
and added that cuz that was definitely
in the original one. So, um, total
duration, patient shall complete at
least two preparation sessions totaling
no less than 3 hours prior to the first
administration. Minimum requirements may
be reduced for subsequent dosing.
Yes. Sorry.
>> [laughter]
>> And And it looks like there's mixed
about whether voting today or taking
some time to digest. So, I would
recommend, uh, since there are some
people who do want to digest it a little
bit, is just holding off on that. Um,
because this is, uh, again, as we've
kind of talked a little bit about, uh,
this isn't so much for the the next set
of rules, um, but more about the best
practices and guidance. So, uh, it's not
imperative that a vote be taken on this
today. So, maybe to allow people that
time to digest since there's a few
comments about that.
>> Yeah, I would be perfectly happy with
giving you guys a chance to digest. Um,
I do know that
the department is pretty busy. So, would
you guys be available for
Monday, the
15th?
>> Also, June 15th at 9:00?
>> Yes.
>> Okay. Cool.
Let me just double check something.
Cool. Yeah, that that looks like it
should work.
>> Perfect. And then, Johnny, will you go
ahead and send uh once the meeting ends,
will you send a copy of the preparation
sessions as amended to all of the
meeting participants?
>> [snorts]
>> Yes.
>> Perfect. All righty, well, we will be
meeting on June 15th at 9:00 a.m.
Um
but thank you guys for spending your
Wednesday morning with us. I really
appreciate you taking the time to be
here, and I'm sure the patients of the
future will appreciate you all taking
the time to put your resources, energy,
research, um
and time into making the program as
safe, effective, and accessible as
possible. I genuinely do thank you all
from the bottom of my heart. It is so
easy to not show up to these meetings,
so the fact that you are here today is a
blessing. Thank you all so much.
>> And thank you on behalf of the
department, everybody. This is really a
lot of great work, and we definitely
want to hear more about what people's
thoughts are, and so thank you, and hope
you all have a great rest of your day.